<resources>
    <string name="app_name">News-Weather app</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="newsPicture_description">Shows picture of the news</string>
    <string name="gigachad_headline">Anyone can become Gigachad</string>
    <string name="gigachad_description">To become like Gigachad you just need one drop of the…</string>
    <string name="lips_headline">New invention</string>
    <string name="lips_description">Result will shock you! To pump your lips you just need…</string>
    <string name="cat_headline">Get a free pussy</string>
    <string name="cat_description">Finally even you have a chance to get a pussy…</string>
    <string name="pipi_headline">From 10cm to 15cm</string>
    <string name="pipi_description">You will be in shock!! Increase your sausage by 5cm in just a month!</string>
    <string name="milf_headline">This hot mom is alone today</string>
    <string name="milf_description">Find easily hot milfs in your area with our new app</string>
    <string name="ointment_headline">Lasting only 2 minutes?</string>
    <string name="ointment_description">Not a problem anymore! Try this new ointment</string>
    <string name="trollface_headline">Old but gold</string>
    <string name="trollface_descriptiom">The legendary meme made its comeback. Read the story of the famous meme.</string>
    <string name="kianu_headline">Modern decease</string>
    <string name="kianu_description">How depression seized the modern generation and what to do.</string>
    <string name="bbc_news">BBC-News(BigBlackCock)</string>
    <string name="picture">picture</string>

    <string name="gigachad_article">\nToday everything is possible! With this magic liquid you can become like Gigachad.
        All you need is just a drop of this liquid named "Simon\'s cum".
        \n\nWho is Gigachad? GigaChad is a nickname associated with the art project berlin.1969
        or Ernest Khalimov,which is a series of photoshopped photographs of several models created by 
        Russian photographer Krista Sudmalis for her project Sleek-N-Tears.
        The name "GigaChad" indicates that the person, who was initially assumed to be real, is the ultimate 
        Chad Thundercock, an internet archetype representing an ultra-masculine, sexually attractive male.Online, 
        the term was popularized within various incel communities.</string>

    <string name="lips_article">\nPump your lips with this brand new shit.
    \nLip augmentation is a cosmetic procedure that modifies the shape of the lips using fillers, 
    such as collagen or implants. The procedure may be performed to increase lip size, correct asymmetry, 
    create protrusion, or adjust the ratio of the top and bottom lips. The procedure typically involves surgical 
    injection, though temporary non-surgical alternatives exist. Swelling and bruising are common after lip augmentation, 
    and irritation or allergic reaction may also occur. Lip augmentations can have undesired cosmetic effects, 
    including scarring and lumping, and implants pose the risk of shifting underneath the lip or breaking through the skin.</string>

    <string name="cat_article">\nGet your free pussy already today. \nPussy Riot is a Russian feminist protest and performance
    art group based in Moscow that became popular for its provocative punk rock music which later
    turned into a more accessible style. Founded in August 2011, it has had a membership of approximately 11 women.
    The group staged unauthorized, provocative guerrilla gigs in public places. These performances were filmed as music
    videos and posted on the internet. The group\'s lyrical themes included feminism, LGBT rights, opposition to Russian
    President Vladimir Putin and his policies, and Putin\'s links to the leadership of the Russian Orthodox Church.</string>

    <string name="pipi_article">\nIncrease your pipi size and get all pussies around you.
        \nA penis (plural penises or penes is the primary sexual organ that male animals use
        to inseminate females (or hermaphrodites) during copulation. Such organs occur in many animals,
        both vertebrate and invertebrate, but males do not bear a penis in every animal species.
        Furthermore, penises are not necessarily homologous.</string>

    <string name="milf_article">\nAn organism\'s sex is female if it produces the ovum (egg cell),
        the type of gamete (sex cell) that fuses with the male gamete (sperm cell) during sexual reproduction.A
        female has larger gametes than a male. Females and males are results of the anisogamous reproduction system,
        wherein gametes are of different sizes (unlike isogamy where they are the same size). The exact mechanism
        of female gamete evolution remains unknown.
        In species that have males and females, sex-determination may be based on either sex chromosomes,
        or environmental conditions. Most female mammals, including female humans, have two X chromosomes.
        Female characteristics vary between different species, with some species having pronounced secondary
        female sex characteristics, such as the presence of pronounced mammary glands in mammals.</string>

    <string name="ointment_article">\nMany men believe that increasing the size of their penises will make them
        a better lover or make them more attractive. But chances are your penis is within the typical size range.Even
        if your penis is smaller than average, it may not matter to your partner. In addition, there\'s no proven way
        to make a penis larger. The solution to your concerns about penis size may be as easy as talking with your
        partner or getting in shape. If those steps don\'t help, try talking with a professional counselor about
        your concerns.</string>

    <string name="trollface_article">\nTrollface was drawn in Microsoft Paint on September 19, 2008, by Carlos Ramirez,
        an 18-year-old Oakland college student. The image was published on Ramirez\'s DeviantArt page, "Whynne",
        as part of a rage comic titled Trolls, about the pointless nature of trolling.Ramirez posted the image
        to the imageboard website 4chan and other users started to share it. In the following months, Ramirez\'s
        drawing quickly gained traction on 4chan as the universal emoticon of an internet troll and a versatile rage
        comic character. From 4chan, Trollface spread to Reddit and Urban Dictionary in 2009, eventually reaching other
        internet image-sharing sites like Imgur and Facebook. In March 2021, Ramirez announced his intention
        to sell a non-fungible token for Trollface.</string>

    <string name="kianu_article">\nThere has been much speculation about modern environments causing an epidemic
        of depression. This review aims to determine whether depression rates have increased and review evidence
        for possible explanations. While available data indicate rising prevalence and an increased lifetime risk
        for younger cohorts, strong conclusions cannot be drawn due to conflicting results and methodological flaws.
        There are numerous potential explanations for changing rates of depression. Cross-cultural studies can be
        useful for identifying likely culprits. General and specific characteristics of modernization correlate
        with higher risk. A positive correlation between a country\’s GDP per capita, as quantitative measure of
        modernization, and lifetime risk of a mood disorder trended toward significance. Mental and physical
        well-being are intimately related. The growing burden of chronic diseases, which arise from an evolutionary
        mismatch between past human environments and modern-day living, may be central to rising rates of depression.
        Declining social capital and greater inequality and loneliness are candidate mediators of a depressiogenic
        social milieu. Modern populations are increasingly overfed, malnourished, sedentary, sunlight-deficient,
        sleep-deprived, and socially-isolated.</string>
</resources>